<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-04-26T00:00:40-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">brae dot page</title><subtitle>My little part of the internet</subtitle><author><name>braden league</name></author><entry><title type="html">first</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/personal/2022/04/25/first.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="first" /><published>2022-04-25T23:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2022-04-25T23:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/personal/2022/04/25/first</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/personal/2022/04/25/first.html">&lt;p&gt;Hello!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today it was announced that &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/AP/status/1518667836062900225&quot;&gt;Elon Musk is buying Twitter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;lol&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a time in my life not to long ago when I wanted a large follower count and lots of engagement on my posts. I think that time has largely past but the urge to tweet thru it has not. I’ve been sharing my life online for almost two decades now, why would I stop now. I was reminded by facebook today of a quality post I made in 2008 that just says “is epic”. That is really quality stuff but I also got a kick out of seeing that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t think I could stop sharing online if I wanted but I have also learned that it is almost more than anything a public journal and primarily for my own enjoyment. Its nice if others see it, its nice when my tweets get a like or a post spawns a fun conversation. Although, most of the time I just want to talk about the anime I am watching or game I am playing or bad music I am making in a 400 or so character posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a million platforms to do this and many more will come and go but since I know enough to be dangerous when it comes to web technologies so I figured why not roll my own. I control all the files, know where everything is being hosted and more or less understand how this all works. This is using a domain I bought for fun a year ago and being hosted on github pages which is provided for free. The blog itself is running &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;jekyll&lt;/a&gt; which I think I’ve heard about in passing over the years but also comes up if you google some variations of “static site CMS open source”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways, I hope you enjoy, I am not leaving &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/bradenleague&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/braden.league/&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/bradenleague/&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&quot;http://discordapp.com/users/83929155183312896&quot;&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/bradenleague/&quot;&gt;Linkedin&lt;/a&gt;, or any other socials for now but I may attempt to move my shitposting to a place I have a bit more control over :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thx for stopping by!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-braebrae&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>braden league</name></author><category term="Personal" /><summary type="html">Hello!</summary></entry></feed>